{ 
    "health": 
    {
        "title":"Health History / Taha Tinana",
        "description" : "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Nam non nisl a metus finibus viverra blandit in augue.",

        "questions" : 
        [
            {
                "question": "Are you registered with a dentist?",                
                "id": "1010",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "Which dentist are you registered with?"
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Are you registered with a doctor?",
                "id": "1020",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "Which doctor are you registered with?"
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you have any serious medical conditions?",
                "id": "1030",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "Please give details:"
                }
            },  
            {
                "question": "Do you take any medication for anything?",
                "id": "1040",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "Please give details:"
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you have any allergies to anything (e.g., penicillin/bees)?",
                "id": "1050",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "Please give details:"
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Did you have your year 8 vaccinations (immunisation injection)?",
                "id": "1060",
                "type": "Radio", 
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Have you recently had a hearing check?",
                "id": "1070",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "When did you have it?"
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Have you recently had a vision check?",
                "id": "1080",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "When did you have it?"
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you wear glasses or contact lenses?",
                "id": "1090",
                "type": "Radio", 
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    "home": 
    {
        "title":"Home/Whanau",
        "questions" : 
        [
            {
                "question": "Who do you live with (e.g., mum, stepdad, nana, cousin, uncle, caregiver, sister, brother, etc.)?",
                "id": "2010",
                "type": "Listing"
            },
            {
                "question": "How are things at home?",
                "id": "2020",
                "type": "Emoji"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are your relationships like with the people you live with?",
                "id": "2030",
                "type": "Emoji"
            },  
            {
                "question": "Do you feel safe at home?",
                "id": "2040",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "No",
                    "question": "Can you explain why?"
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Is there someone at home you can talk to if you feel upset or who you could go to if you needed help with a problem?",
                "id": "2050",
                "type": "Radio", 
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Have there been any big changes in your family or at home recently (e.g., moving, someone leaving, someone new)?",
                "id": "2060",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "What have the changes been?"
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you or your caregivers worry about not having enough money for essential things (e.g., food, clothes, school equipment, petrol for the car)?",
                "id": "2070",
                "type": "Radio", 
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "What jobs or responsibilities do you have at home (e.g., chores like dishes, looking after siblings)?",
                "id": "2080",
                "type": "TextForm"
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you ever feel like you have too much responsibility?",
                "id": "2090",
                "type": "Radio", 
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you have rules you need to stick to at home (e.g., always tidy up after yourself, no smoking, curfew)?",
                "id": "2100",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "What are some of these rules?"
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Who makes the rules in your house (e.g., dad, mum, both, older brother, or sister)?",
                "id": "2110",
                "type": "TextForm"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the consequences for breaking the rules (e.g., grounded, phone confiscated, hiding)?",
                "id": "2120",
                "type": "TextForm"
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you think the rules and consequences are FAIR or UNFAIR?",
                "id": "2130",
                "type": "Radio", 
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Fair"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "Unfair"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "What do you like to do with your family for fun (e.g., go swimming together, camping, hunting, games, road trips)?",
                "id": "21400",
                "type": "TextForm"
            }
            
        ]
    },     
  "education and employment": 
    {
    "title":"Education and Employment",
    "questions" : 
        [
            {
                "question": "What do you like about school?",
                "id": "3010",
                "type": "TextForm"
            },
            {
                "question": "What don't you like about school?",
                "id": "3020",
                "type": "TextForm"
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you think you need extra help with any subjects at school?",
                "id": "3030",
                "type": "YNifSo",
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "Which subject(s)?"
                }
            },  
            {
                "question": "How well do you get along with the teachers at school?",
                "id": "3040",
                "type": "Emoji"
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you feel the teachers are fair?",
                "id": "3050",
                "type": "Radio",
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "Some"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you feel the adults at school care about you?",
                "id": "3060",
                "type": "Radio",
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "Some"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Are there adults at school you feel you could talk to about something important or personal?",
                "id": "3070",
                "type": "Radio",
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you ever skip classes?",
                "id": "3080",
                "type": "Radio",
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Never"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "Once"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "Occasionally"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "Lots"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "How well do you get on with other students?",
                "id": "3090",
                "type": "Emoji"
            },
            {
                "question": "Are you being bullied in any way?",
                "id": "3100",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "In what way?"
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Are you doing any work outside of school (e.g., a job)?",
                "id": "3150",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "What work do you do?"
                }
            },           
            {
                "question": "Any idea of what you want to do when you have finished school?",
                "id": "3160",
                "type": "TextForm"
            }
        ]
    },
    "nutrition": {
      "title": "Nutrition and Exercise",    
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "How much exercise do you do in an average week?",
          "id": "4000",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": 
          [
            {
                "answer": "None"
            },
            {
                "answer": "At least twice a week"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Most days"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Every day"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "What do you like to do for exercise?",
          "id": "4010",
          "type": "Listing"
        },
        {
          "question": "Most days do you have...",
          "id":"4100",
          "type": "Checkbox",
          "responses": [
            {
              "answer": "Breakfast"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Lunch"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Dinner"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "How many times a week would someone in your home cook you dinner?",
          "id": "4200",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": 
          [
            {
                "answer": "Every day"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Most days"
            },
            {
              "answer": "More than 3 times a week"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Less than 3 times a week"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Never"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "How often would you have a sugary drink (e.g.,  fizzy, energy drinks, cordial, Raro)?",
          "id":"4300",
          "type": "TextForm"        
        },
        {
          "question": "Do you think you have a healthy diet?",
          "id": "4400",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": 
          [
            {
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "answer": "No"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Sometimes when people are stressed they can over-eat or under-eat. Do you find yourself doing either of these?",
          "id": "4500",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": 
          [
            {
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "answer": "No"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Sometimes"
          }
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Have there been any big changes in your weight or in your dietary habits (what you eat and how often)?",
          "id": "4600",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": 
          [
            {
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "answer": "No"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Are you happy with your weight?",
          "id": "4700",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": 
          [
            {
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "answer": "No"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "activities": 
    {
        "title":"Activities",
        "description" : "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Nam non nisl a metus finibus viverra blandit in augue.",

        "questions" : 
        [
            {
                "question": "What do you like to do for fun?",
                "id": "5010",
                "type": "Listing"
            },
            {
              "question": "How do you spend your time when you're not at school?",
              "id": "5020",
              "type": "Listing"
            },
            {
              "question": "Do you like...",
              "id": "5030",
              "type": "Radio",
              "responses": [
                {
                  "answer": "To spend time with friends"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Prefer to be by yourself"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "Both"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "question": "When you are with your friends, what do you do?",
              "id":"5040",
              "type": "TextForm",
              "conditions": {
                "target": "5030",
                "compare": "=*",
                "value": ["To spend time with friends", "Both"]
              }
            },
            {
                "question": "How do you think your friends would describe you?",
                "id":"5050",
                "type": "TextForm",
                "conditions": {
                  "target": "5030",
                  "compare": "=*",
                  "value": ["To spend time with friends", "Both"]
                }
            },
            {
              "question": "Are you involved in any of the following...",
              "id":"5060",
              "type": "Checkbox",
              "responses": [
                {
                  "answer": "music"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "church"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "kapahaka"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "drama"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "dance"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "sports"
                },
                {
                  "answer": "clubs/scouts"
                }
              ]
            },
            {
              "question": "is there a sport or activity that you would like to do but cant?",
                  "id": "5070",
                  "type": "YNifSo", 
                  "ifSo": {
                      "val": "Yes",
                      "question": "What is stopping you from doing this?"
                  }
            }
        ]
    },
    "technology and social media": 
    {
        "title":"Technology and Social Media",
        "questions" : 
        [
            {
                "question": "How much screen time do you have a day (TV/Internet) in hours?",
                "id": "6010",
                "type": "TextForm"
            },
            {
              "question": "Have you sent messages or images to other people that you later regretted?",
              "id": "6020",
              "type": "Radio", 
              "responses": [
                  {
                      "answer": "Yes"
                  },
                  {
                      "answer": "No"
                  }
              ]
            },
            {
              "question": "What do you mainly use the internet for?",
              "id": "6030",
              "type": "TextForm"
            },
            {
              "question": "In what ways can you keep yourself safe when using social media (e.g., 'I don't share my address with someone I don't know')? What are your ideas?",
              "id":"6040",
              "type": "Listing"
            }
        ]
    },

        "drugs": {
            "title": "Substance Use",
            "description": "This information will not be passed on without your permission.",
            "questions": [
        {"question": "Do you smoke cigarettes / tobacco?",
          "id": "7000",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": [
              {
                  "answer": "No"
              },
              {
                  "answer": "Tried it didn’t like it"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Now and again"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Weekly"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Daily"
              }
          ]
        },
        {"question": "Do you ever have a drink containing alcohol?",
          "id": "7100",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": [
              {
                  "answer": "No"
              },
              {
                  "answer": "Tried it didn’t like it"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Now and again"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Weekly"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Daily"
              }
          ]
        },
        {"question": "Have you ever used weed (cannabis)?",
          "id": "7200",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": [
              {
                  "answer": "No"
              },
              {
                  "answer": "Tried it didn’t like it"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Now and again"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Weekly"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Daily"
              }
          ]
        },
        {"question": "Have you ever used P (meth)?",
          "id": "7300",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": [
              {
                  "answer": "No"
              },
              {
                  "answer": "Tried it didn’t like it"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Now and again"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Weekly"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Daily"
              }
          ]
        },
        {"question": "Have you ever used synthetics?",
          "id": "7400",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": [
              {
                  "answer": "No"
              },
              {
                  "answer": "Tried it didn’t like it"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Now and again"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Weekly"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Daily"
              }
          ]
        },
        {"question": "Have you ever used solvents(Huffing)?",
          "id": "7500",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": [
              {
                  "answer": "No"
              },
              {
                  "answer": "Tried it didn’t like it"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Now and again"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Weekly"
              },
              {
                "answer": "Daily"
              }
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Are there any other substances you have used?",
          "id":"7600",
          "type": "TextForm"
        },
        {"question": "Would you like to speak to someone about substance use, or get help with stopping?",
          "id": "7700",
          "type": "Radio", 
          "responses": [
              {
                  "answer": "Yes"
              },
              {
                  "answer": "No"
              }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "emotional health": {
        "title": "Emotional Health",
        "description": "If any of the answers to the following questions change for you, or you feel you need further support, please see the: school nurse, school counsellor or REAL, your school dean.",
        "questions": [
    {"question": "In the past few months have you felt sad more than you have felt happy?",
      "id": "8000",
      "type": "Radio", 
      "responses": [
          {
              "answer": "Yes"
          },
          {
              "answer": "No"
          }
      ]
    },
    {"question": "Do you feel good about yourself?",
      "id": "8100",
      "type": "Radio", 
      "responses": [
          {
              "answer": "Yes"
          },
          {
              "answer": "No"
          },
          {
            "answer": "Sometimes"
          }
      ]
    },
    {"question": "Are you getting any help from anyone for problems you've had (e.g., counselor)?",
      "id": "8200",
      "type": "YNifSo", 
      "ifSo": 
          {
              "val": "Yes",
              "question": "If so, who?"
          }

    },
    {"question": "Do you ever think life is not worth living?",
      "id": "8300",
      "type": "Radio", 
      "responses": [
          {
              "answer": "Yes"
          },
          {
              "answer": "No"
          },
          {
            "answer": "Sometimes"
          }
      ]
    },
    {"question": "Do you ever think about hurting yourself?",
      "id": "8400",
      "type": "Radio", 
      "responses": [
          {
              "answer": "Yes"
          },
          {
              "answer": "No"
          },
          {
            "answer": "Sometimes"
          }
      ]
    },
    {"question": "Have you ever done anything to hurt yourself on purpose?",
      "id": "8500",
      "type": "Radio", 
      "responses": [
        {    
            "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "answer": "No"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you think you feel most of the time?",
      "id":"8600",
      "type": "Emoji"
    },
    {"question": "Is there anything in your life right now that is causing you a lot of stress?",
      "id": "8700",
      "type": "YNifSo", 
      "ifSo": 
      {
          "val": "Yes",
          "question": "If so, what?"
      }
    },
    {"question": "Has anyone close to you committed suicide?",
        "id": "8800",
        "type": "Radio", 
        "responses": [
          {    
              "answer": "Yes"
          },
          {
              "answer": "No"
          }
        ]
      },
      {"question": "Do you need any more help around this?",
        "id": "8900",
        "type": "Radio", 
        "responses": [
          {    
              "answer": "Yes"
          },
          {
              "answer": "No"
          }
        ]
      }
  ],
  "footer" : "If today or recently, you have felt really low, suicidal or are self-harming, please see one of the following people today or as soon as possible: school nurse, school consellor or REAl or your school dean."
},
"sexualHealth": 
    {
        "title":"Sexuality and Sexual Health",
        "description" : [ "We ask all young people about sexuality and sexual health because it's an important area of health and wellbeing. Having good sexual health is about being comfortable with your sexuality and the decisions you make about sex.  It also involves building emotional maturity, relationship skills and a healthy body image.  It helps you make the right decision for you about sex so that when you’re ready your sexual experiences and relationships are positive, safe and respectful. ", "This information will stay completely private. It does not get shared with anyone else other than the nurse." ],
        "questions" : 
        [
            {
                "question": "Is there anything in particular that you’d like to talk to the school health person about?",
                "id": "9010",
                "type": "TextForm"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who are you attracted to?",
                "id": "9020",
                "type": "Slider",
                "responses": 
                    {
                        "right": "Female",
                        "left": "Male",
                        "check": "No one"
                    }
            },
            {
                "question": "I think I have a good understanding about sex.",
                "id": "9040",
                "type": "Slider",
                "risk": 0.2,
                "resiliency": 0.4,
                "responses": 
                    {
                        "right": "No, don't understand much at all",
                        "left": "Yes, I know I get it"
                    }
            },
            {
                "question": "I feel comfortable talking about sex and sexuality with people I trust.",
                "id": "9050",
                "type": "Slider",
                "risk": 0.4,
                "resiliency": 0.6,
                "tooltip": {
                    "questionArr": ["I feel comfortable talking about sex and", " with people I trust"],
                    "wordArr": ["sexuality"],
                    "defArr": ["one of those things you’re born with, you do not choose it, it’s just part of who you are, whether you be physically, emotionally and sexually attracted to males, female or both."]
                  },
                "responses": 
                    {
                        "right": "No, I feel very uncomfortable",
                        "left": "Yes, I feel comfortable"
                    }
            },
            {
                "question": "I know what the  term ‘safe sex’ means. ",
                "id": "9060",
                "type": "Slider",
                "risk": 0.5,
                "resiliency": 0.5,
                "responses": 
                    {
                        "right": "No, I don't understand much at all",
                        "left": "Yes, I know I get it"
                    }
            },
            {
                "question": "Have you been in a relationship or regularly seen anyone?",
                "id": "9070",
                "type": "Radio",
                "responses": [
                  {
                    "answer": "Yes"
                  },
                  {
                    "answer": "No"
                  }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Have you ever had a sexual relationship with:",
                "id": "9080",
                "type": "Checkbox",
                "risk": 8,
                "responses": [
                  {
                    "answer": "Boy"
                  },
                  {
                    "answer": "Girl"
                  },
                  {
                    "answer": "Other"
                  }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Are you in a sexual relationship currently?",
                "id": "9090",
                "type": "Radio",
                "conditions": 
                {
                    "target": "9080",
                    "compare": "any",
                    "value": null
                  },
                "responses": [
                  {
                    "answer": "Yes",
                    "risk": 8
                  },
                  {
                    "answer": "No"
                  }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you feel comfortable and safe being sexual active?",
                "id": "9100",
                "type": "Slider",
                "risk": 1,
                "resiliency": 1,
                "conditions": 
                {
                    "target": "9090",
                    "compare": "=",
                    "value": "Yes"
                },
                "responses": 
                    {
                        "right": "No",
                        "left": "Yes"
                    }
            },
            {
                "question": "If you’d like to ask us any questions or let us know anything, or add any comments please do this below.",
                "id": "9110",
                "type": "TextForm"
            },
            {
                "question": "We ask all young people we see about sexual harm, we do this because we want to support you to be safe. If you’re uncomfortable you can chat with the health professional afterwards. Please remember this will be treated within the boundaries of confidentiality.",
                "id": "9120",
                "type": "AddInfo",
                "tooltip": {
                    "questionArr": ["We ask all young people we see about", ", we do this because we want to support you to be safe. If you’re uncomfortable you can chat with the health professional afterwards. Please remember this will be treated within the boundaries of confidentiality."],
                    "wordArr": ["sexual harm"],
                    "defArr": ["When someone has a sexual experience they don't want, or are forced into any kind of sexual act by another person"]
                  }
            },
            {
                "question": "Have you ever been touched in a sexual way you did not like or agree to?",
                
                "id": "9130",
                "type": "Radio",
                "responses": [
                  {
                    "answer": "Yes",
                    "risk": 10
                  },  
                  {
                    "answer": "No"
                  },
                  {
                    "answer": "Maybe",
                    "risk": 8
                  },
                  {
                    "answer": "Unsure",
                    "risk": 8
                  }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you feel safe at the moment? (This is something the health professional will talk with you more about when you see them for your 1:1 session.)",
                "id": "9140",
                "type": "Radio",
                "conditions": 
                {
                    "target": "9130",
                    "compare": "=",
                    "value": "Yes"
                },
                "responses": [
                        {
                            "answer": "Yes"
                        },
                        {
                            "answer": "No",
                            "risk": 10
                        }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Some young people are looking at porn on the internet. There can be a number of reasons someone may do this, and sometimes we’re not sure how we feel about what we do see. The reason we’re going to  ask you questions about porn is because we want to support you in being safe. It’s really good to be honest about this as the answers you put may help you understand where you’re at with this a lot better.",
                "id": "9150",
                "type": "AddInfo"                
            },
            {
                "question": "Have you seen sexual images, (ie. porn) that you chose to view",
                "id": "9160",
                "type": "Radio",
                "responses": [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes",
                        "risk": 2
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No",
                        "resilency": 3
                   }
                ] 
            },
            {
                "question": "How did you feel about this?",
                "id": "9170",
                "type": "Slider",
                "conditions": 
                {
                    "target": "9160",
                    "compare": "=",
                    "value": "Yes"
                },
                "responses": 
                    {
                        "right": "Uncomfortable",
                        "left": "Fine"
                    }
            },
            {
                "question": "Have you seen sexual images, (ie. porn) that you DIDN'T choose to view",
                "id": "9171",
                "type": "Radio",
                "responses": [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes",
                        "risk": 8
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                   }
                ] 
            },
            {
                "question": "How did you feel about this?",
                "id": "9172",
                "type": "Slider",
                "conditions": 
                {
                    "target": "9171",
                    "compare": "=",
                    "value": "Yes"
                },
                "responses": 
                    {
                        "right": "Uncomfortable",
                        "left": "Fine"
                    }
            },
            {
                "question": "How often do you view pornography?",
                "id": "9180",
                "type": "Slider",
                "risk": 0.7,
                "resiliency": 0.5,
                "conditions": 
                {
                    "target": ["9160","9171"],
                    "compare": "||>",
                    "value": "1"
                },
                "responses": 
                    {
                        "right": "Every day",
                        "left": "Hardly ever"
                    }
            },
            {
                "question": "If you’d like to ask us any questions or let us know anything, or add any comments please do this below",
                "id": "9190",
                "type": "TextForm"
            }
        ]
    },
    "safety": 
    {
      "title":"Safety",
      "description" : "If any of the answers to the following questions change for you, or you feel you need further support please see the: school nurse, school counsellor or REAL or your school dean",
      "questions" : 
      [
        {
          "question": "Is there anyone in your life you are afraid of or who hurts you in any way?",
          "id": "10000",
          "type": "Radio",
          "responses": [
              {
                  "answer": "Yes"
              },
              {
                  "answer": "No"
              }
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Are you afraid of violence in your school/neighbourhood?",
          "id": "10010",
          "type": "YNifSo",
          "ifSo": 
            {
                "val": "Yes",
                "question": "If yes, then where?"
            }
        },
        {
          "question": "Do you ever get in to fights?",
          "id": "10030",
          "type": "Radio",
          "responses": [
            {
              "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
              "answer": "No"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "Do you ever find it hard to keep your anger under control?",
          "id": "10040",
          "type": "Radio",
          "responses": [
            {
              "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
              "answer": "No"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "What do you do when you're angry? (E.g. Go to your room / shout / punch something)",
          "id": "10050",
          "type": "TextForm"
        },
        {
          "question": "Have you ever been physically assaulted? (hit/punched/bashed)",
          "id": "10070",
          "type": "Radio",
          "responses": [
            {
              "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
              "answer": "No"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "How often would you wear a seatbelt in a car?",
          "id": "10080",
          "type": "Radio",
          "responses": [
            {
              "answer": "All the time"
            },  
            {
              "answer": "Sometimes"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Never"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
        "question": "Have you ever met in person (or planned to meet) with anyone you have met online?",
        "id": "10090",
        "type": "Radio",
        "responses": [
          {
              "answer": "Yes"
          },
          {
              "answer": "No"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]                   
    },
    "spirit": 
    {
        "title":"Spiritual Health / Wairuatanga",
        "description": "Spirituality means different things to different people. Spirituality is our sense of connection to something bigger than us. It may include a search for beliefs and values; a sense of meaning and a purpose in life; a sense of connectedness; identity and awareness; and for some people, religion.",
        "questions" : 
        [
            {
                "question": "Are you connected to a certain religion/faith/culture or spiritual belief (e.g., Ratana/Christian/Buddhist/Muslim)?",
                "id": "11000",
                "type": "YNifSo", 
                "ifSo": 
                {
                    "val": "Yes",
                    "question": "Which one are you connected with?"
                }
            },
            {
                "question": "Is this something that is important to you?",
                "id": "11010",
                "type": "Radio", 
                "conditions": 
                {
                    "target": "11000",
                    "compare": "=",
                    "value": "Yes"
                  },
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Do you have a wish to change that and connect with something on a deeper level?",
                "id": "11030",
                "type": "Radio",
                "conditions": 
                {
                    "target": "11000",
                    "compare": "=",
                    "value": "No"
                  },
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ]
            },  
            {
                "question": "Do you have a strong connection with your culture that is a spiritual one for you?",
                "id": "11100",
                "type": "Radio", 
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "question": "Is this something you would like to change?",
                "id": "11110",
                "type": "Radio", 
                "conditions": 
                {
                    "target": "11100",
                    "compare": "=",
                    "value": "No"
                  },
                "responses": 
                [
                    {
                        "answer": "Yes"
                    },
                    {
                        "answer": "No"
                    }
                ]
            }
        ],
        "footer" : "If there are any areas of concern that come from this assessment, the nurse will see you. If you’d like to see the nurse then please feel free to drop into the clinic"
    }  
}
